Ana Chkhaidze: That's when I started, I think
Ana Chkhaidze: initially, it was very jarring. And it took a second for my eyes to
Ana Chkhaidze: settle in and I think it. I was very awake when it started, because it caught me off guard. And then I didn't start seeing any
Ana Chkhaidze: shapes or anything until
Ana Chkhaidze: well, I would guess, maybe like a minute in, and I would see one shape, and then it would. The second. I think the issue is that when I thought about oh, I'm seeing something. Let me
Ana Chkhaidze: swipe right to say that I was showing something then like it would disappear, or if I saw something, and I swipe right, and then I noticed that it started speeding up, and I started to like, do the counterclockwise movement. Then it would disappear because I was like thinking about it instead of dissociating anymore.
Ana Chkhaidze: But once I got, I think, deeper into the watching it, it
Ana Chkhaidze: started to all blend together. And I I just saw a lot of shapes spinning and rotating, and lines forming, and
Ana Chkhaidze: and they just kept shifting every time I thought to
Ana Chkhaidze: like. Take notice of it with the remote control. And then I I just got really tired towards the end. I feel like in the beginning. I was wide awake and paying attention and watching, and then at the end, I was struggling to keep my eyes open, not necessarily from boredom. I feel like. They went by a lot faster than I thought, but more so from
Ana Chkhaidze: just the like, just soting, disassociating, and eyes glazing over. I think it made me more tired.
Ana Chkhaidze: And it went by way quicker than I thought, and I think I feel like that's it.
Ana Chkhaidze: So
Ana Chkhaidze: it's like, I think that's it. Sorry.